

LORALEE STARLA GENTRY

FILM PRODUCTION & DIGITAL MEDIA DESIGN

832 - 444 - 9799

loraleestarla@me.com

5457 Laurel Canyon Blvd, #108 Valley Village, CA 91607

www.loraleestarla.com

ABOUT ME

Creative individual with extensive knowledge and industry experience in Film Production, Visual and Graphic Design, and Web Design.

Strong passion for creating and expanding stories portrayed through visual mediums.

Motivated to entertain and inspire communities through illustrative and interactive user experiences.

WORK HISTORY

JAN 2016

APR 2014

AUG 2012

OCT 2012

NEW MEDIA OPERATOR

Los Angeles Duplication and Broadcasting (LADB) | Burbank, CA January 2016 - Present

Post-production shift lead focusing on providing content for clients per their specifications, while following ISO and MPAA security regulations. Perform encoding, transcoding, and editing of HD and SD video formats. Handle all aspects of DVD and Blu-Ray creation from motion or still menus and navigation, graphics, authoring, and duplication, to finished packaging. Provide digital asset management, forensic watermarking, aspect ratio conversions, and quality control.

MEDIA PRODUCTION ASSISTANT

Eastern Washington University | Cheney, WA April 2014 - June 2015

Key member of the video production team for Eastern Washington University's extended campus, online division. Filmed events and interviews on location. Did production design, grip, lighting, and camera work for videos filmed in studio and on location. Compiled and organized HD, SD, audio, and still footage. Edited audio and video content along with creating and merging digital graphics and effects for complete final product. Used design principles and creative thinking to produce innovative and visually interesting videos.

BEAUTY ADVISOR

Walgreens Drug Store | Seattle, WA August 2012 - June 2013

Greeted customers and assisted them with finding the right products for their specific needs. Organized and cleaned designated aisles of the store to create a better shopping experience for customers and move more merchandise. Rang up customers at the register and successfully handled cash, card, and check transactions.

SECRETARY ON THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS

Diverse Harmony | Seattle, WA October 2012 - June 2013

Board member for the 501(c)(3) non-profit Gay-Straight Alliance Youth Chorus of Seattle. Recorded official meeting minutes, kept a compilation of all important documents, and made decisions on behalf of the chorus by voting as a board member on financial, organizational, administrative, and creative issues.

REFERENCES

- KRISTINE FEBRE LOS ANGELES DUPLICATION AND BROADCASTING New Media Manager | 818-620-6466
- **COREY BURGESS EASTERN WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY** Media Production Specialist | 509-359-6284
- MARY CUTHBERT WALGREENS Store Manager | 206-709-4569

EDUCATION

EASTERN WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY

Cheney, WA | Sept 2013 - June 2015

Bachelor of Arts Degree Interdisiplinary Studies, focused in Film Production and Digital Media Design

SEATTLE CENTRAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE

Seattle, WA | April 2011 - June 2013

Associate of Arts Degree **General Studies**

CALIFORNIA POLYTECHNIC STATE UNIVERSITY

San Luis Obispo, CA | Sept 2008 - June 2012 Studied Aerospace Engineering

CLEAR LAKE HIGH SCHOOL

Houston, TX | Sept 2004 - June 2008 Diploma

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

I HOI EGGIOTIAL	JIXI				
ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS			85%		
ADOBE ENCORE				95%	
ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR			90	1%	
ADOBE INDESIGN			90	1%	
ADOBE MEDIA ENCODER				95%	
ADOBE PHOTOSHOP				95%	
ADOBE PREMIERE PRO				95%	
CLIPSTER	65%				
COMPRESSOR 3 AND 4				95%	
CSS 3 / HTML 5 / JAVASCRIP	Т	80)%		
DIGITAL RAPIDS - STREAMZ	70)%			
DVD STUDIO PRO				95%	
FILEMAKER				95%	
FINAL CUT PRO 7 AND X				95%	
IWORKS/MICROSOFT OFFICE				95%	
RHOZET CARBON CODER		75%			
	ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS ADOBE ENCORE ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR ADOBE INDESIGN ADOBE MEDIA ENCODER ADOBE PHOTOSHOP ADOBE PREMIERE PRO CLIPSTER COMPRESSOR 3 AND 4 CSS 3 / HTML 5 / JAVASCRIP DIGITAL RAPIDS - STREAMZ DVD STUDIO PRO FILEMAKER FINAL CUT PRO 7 AND X IWORKS/MICROSOFT OFFICE	ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS ADOBE ENCORE ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR ADOBE INDESIGN ADOBE MEDIA ENCODER ADOBE PHOTOSHOP ADOBE PREMIERE PRO CLIPSTER 65% COMPRESSOR 3 AND 4 CSS 3 / HTML 5 / JAVASCRIPT DIGITAL RAPIDS - STREAMZ 70 DVD STUDIO PRO FILEMAKER FINAL CUT PRO 7 AND X IWORKS/MICROSOFT OFFICE	ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS ADOBE ENCORE ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR ADOBE INDESIGN ADOBE MEDIA ENCODER ADOBE PHOTOSHOP ADOBE PREMIERE PRO CLIPSTER 65% COMPRESSOR 3 AND 4 CSS 3 / HTML 5 / JAVASCRIPT 80 DIGITAL RAPIDS - STREAMZ 70% DVD STUDIO PRO FILEMAKER FINAL CUT PRO 7 AND X IWORKS/MICROSOFT OFFICE	ADOBE ENCORE ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR 90 ADOBE INDESIGN 90 ADOBE MEDIA ENCODER ADOBE PHOTOSHOP ADOBE PREMIERE PRO CLIPSTER 65% COMPRESSOR 3 AND 4 CSS 3 / HTML 5 / JAVASCRIPT 80% DVD STUDIO PRO FILEMAKER FINAL CUT PRO 7 AND X IWORKS/MICROSOFT OFFICE	ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS 85% ADOBE ENCORE 95% ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR 90% ADOBE INDESIGN 90% ADOBE MEDIA ENCODER 95% ADOBE PHOTOSHOP 95% ADOBE PREMIERE PRO 95% CLIPSTER 65% COMPRESSOR 3 AND 4 95% CSS 3 / HTML 5 / JAVASCRIPT 80% DIGITAL RAPIDS - STREAMZ 70% DVD STUDIO PRO 95% FILEMAKER 95% FINAL CUT PRO 7 AND X 95% IWORKS/MICROSOFT OFFICE 95%

PERSONAL SKILLS









TO DETAIL





SOLVING

INNOVATION

PEOPLE SKILLS

COMMUNICATION PASSION